<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>COMP3601 21T3 | Team Orange 🍊</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on COMP3601 21T3 | Team Orange 🍊</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:49:43 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Progress - Week 8</title><link>/progress/week8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 22:49:43 +1100</pubDate><guid>/progress/week8/</guid><description>Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Week 8 Progress Update
Schedule Blocking - Matrix Multiplication
Development of the MCU Main Control Unit created to co-ordinate signals Two operating modes Encryption Decryption Dot Product Next steps: Multiplier
Optimising the Encryption Stage Issue: Current row selection is biased
i.e 10% selection chance / 90% not selected</description></item><item><title>Progress - Week 7</title><link>/progress/week7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 22:49:43 +1100</pubDate><guid>/progress/week7/</guid><description>Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Week 7 Progress Update
Schedule Interfacing Streaming ASCII
Sending messages between devices requires conversion The VHDL standard libraries can be used for text I/O Contents of a file on the sender&amp;rsquo;s computer is extracted as bits and passed into the LWE system The file reader must sync to the clock of the MCU Xoroshiro RNG Optimisations for space</description></item><item><title>Progress - Weeks 5 &amp; 6</title><link>/progress/week5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 22:49:43 +1100</pubDate><guid>/progress/week5/</guid><description>Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Week 5 &amp;amp; 6 Progress Update
Schedule Matlab [MATLAB Analysis]
PSA: MATLAB isn&amp;rsquo;t a coding language - Andrew Wong Decryption Module Designed like a state machine Optimisation: Subtract q/4 from all sides of the inequality Allows a simpler (faster!) comparison of D &amp;lt; q/2 Updated Components Updated port definitions to limit n</description></item><item><title>Progress - Week 4</title><link>/progress/week4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 22:49:44 +1100</pubDate><guid>/progress/week4/</guid><description>Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Week 5 Progress Update
Schedule Encryption not yet completed&amp;hellip; but decryption works!
Decryption Module Current bottleneck is the multiplication.
Perhaps pipeline the multiplication?
Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Thank You! 🍊</description></item><item><title>Progress - Week 3</title><link>/progress/week3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 22:49:43 +1100</pubDate><guid>/progress/week3/</guid><description>Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Week 4 Progress Update
Schedule Didn&amp;rsquo;t get up to testing the RNG and Multiplier units.
Testing extended to Week 4
VHDL Components BEFORE
Fleshed out the specifications for the components AFTER
In that process, we also identified a few possible issues and overheads that would make the logic area large Connection Diagram How Big?</description></item><item><title>Progress - Week 2</title><link>/progress/week2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 19:13:50 +1100</pubDate><guid>/progress/week2/</guid><description>Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Week 2 Progress Update
Progress This Week Changes to the Gantt Chart RNG implementation has been extended into week 3 Multiplication pushed back as implementation was discussed in Thursday lecture Need for a modulo function Need to generate prime numbers More research needed to be conducted in week 2 than anticipated Random Number Generator Current Implementation</description></item><item><title>Progress - Week 1</title><link>/progress/week1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 19:13:46 +1100</pubDate><guid>/progress/week1/</guid><description>COMP3601 21T2 Project
Team Orange 🍊 Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian Table of Contents Task Breakdown Gantt Chart Progress made over the past week Tasks for upcoming weeks The Team Andrew Nicholson 3rd Year ElecEng / CompSci Andrew Wong 4th Year CompEng Arpit Rulania 3rd Year CompEng Ziyue Lian 4th Year CompEng Task Breakdown Random Number Generator Multiplier Keygen Module Encryption Module Decryption Module Gantt Chart Progress Made So Far Matlab model of LWE completed Gantt chart made Project broken down into manageable tasks Research Block Diagram Future Tasks Research methods of implementation.</description></item><item><title>MATLAB Model</title><link>/matlab-model/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 22:49:43 +1100</pubDate><guid>/matlab-model/</guid><description>-- -- iframe.viz { background-color: rgba(255,255,255,0.85); height: 100vh; width: 100%; overflow-y: hidden; transition: background-color 0.3s; } iframe.viz:hover { background-color: rgba(255,255,255,1); } .resp-container { max-height: 600px; overflow-y: hidden; } Team Orange Andrew Nicholson Andrew Wong Arpit Rulania Ziyue Lian A look at our MATLAB model&amp;hellip;
Brought to you by featherbear and his hatred towards MATLAB MATLAB Model function S = generatePrivateKey(m) global q; S = randi(q, [m, 1]); end function [A, B] = generatePublicKey(S, m, n) global q; A = randi(q, [n, m]); e = round(randn(n, 1)); B = mod(A*S, q) + e; end function [u, v] = encryptBit(M, A, B) global q; sampleSize = fix(numel(B) / 4); samplesChoices = randsample(1:length(B), sampleSize); u = mod(sum(A(samplesChoices,:)), q); v = mod(sum(B(samplesChoices,:)) - M * fix(q/2), q); end function M = decryptBit(u, v, S) global q; D = mod(v - dot(S, u), q) M = D &amp;gt; q/4 &amp;amp; D &amp;lt; 3*q/4; end Source: lwe.</description></item></channel></rss>